Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 75, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Hemispheric Trade Union News, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.34
  - Item 10: Hemispheric Trade Union News, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.36
  - Item 11: Hemispheric Trade Union News, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: monthly bulletin
  - Item 12: Hemispheric Trade Union News, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.41
  - Item 13: Hemispheric Trade Union News, 1980; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.43
  - Item 14: Hemispheric Trade Union News, 1980; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.44
  - Item 15: Hemispheric Trade Union News, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.39
  - Item 16: African trade unions and employment policies, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
- Box: 75, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: I.F.J. information, 1976; Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
    Author: International Federation of Journalists
    Notes: 26
  - Item 2: Idealism in action; the story of the IFJ, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Box: 75, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: International teachers news, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: World Federation of Teachers' Unions
  - Item 2: International Labour Conference 1977: Pulbic Employees' Trade Union Right, Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: International Federation of Free Teachers Unions
    Notes: Feb-77
  - Item 3: Africa, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: Jan-77
  - Item 4: Public Services International holds Congress, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: Oct-77
  - Item 5: Trade union rights for civil servants, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: Sep-77
  - Item 6: Important victory of the Trade Union common front of the Public Service at the I.L.O., 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: Jun-77
  - Item 7: Utopia come true, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: May-77
  - Item 8: In Asia: Progress of IFFTU's Regional Action, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: Apr.-77
  - Item 9: Human rights: guarantee every collective and individual freedom, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Notes: Mar-77
  - Item 10: Industrial relations face hard challenges in the eighties, says ILO Director-General, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: International Labour Office
  - Item 11: Industrial relations face hard challenges in the eighties, says ILO Director-General, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: B.C. Federation of Labour
  - Item 13: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Industrial Relations face hard challenges in the Eeighties, says ILO Director-General, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: International Studies on Technology in Commerce and Industry predict widespread effects on employment and nature of work, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: International Federation of Commercial, Clerical and Professional and Technical Employees
  - Item 21: Information presse, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: European Trade Union Confederation
  - Item 22: Information presse, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: FISE information letter, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Constitution, 1972; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Author: International Federation of Free Teachers' Unions
- Box: 75, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Constitution of F.I.S.E., 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Box: 75, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Heart and soul to Turkey, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Xith Statutory Conference of FISE, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Xith Statutory Conference of FISE, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Xith Statutory Conference of FISE, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Xith Statutory Conference of FISE, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Plan of work for 1990, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Bulletin: Peace, Disarmament, Education, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: FISE/Info, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
    Notes: Aug-88
  - Item 9: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
    Notes: Copy 2.
- Box: 75, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Constitution: including the amendments adopted by the 12th Statutory Conference of the FISE, Budapest, June 12th, 1981, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Constitution of F.I.S.E., 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: XIth statutory conference of FISE: information and documents :Moscow, USSR, June 27-July 1, 1977, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: XIth statutory conference of FISE: information and documents :Moscow, USSR, June 27-July 1, 1977, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Apr-87
  - Item 9: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Jun-87
  - Item 10: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: 3
  - Item 11: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: 0/87
  - Item 17: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: May-87
  - Item 19: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Sep-87
  - Item 20: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Aug-87
  - Item 21: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Oct-87
  - Item 24: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Nov-87
  - Item 25: FISE information letter, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Feb-88
  - Item 26: FISE information letter, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Mar-88
  - Item 27: FISE information letter, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Apr-88
  - Item 28: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 29: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 30: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: 7
  - Item 31: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 32: FISE information letter, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 33: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 34: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 35: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 36: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Jul-87
  - Item 37: FISE Infos, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 38: FISE Infos, 1989; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Mar-89
  - Item 39: FISE Infos, 1990; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Apr-90
  - Item 40: FISE Infos, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 41: FISE Infos, 1989; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: Feb-89
  - Item 42: FISE Infos, 1990; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 43: Education for peace, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Box: 75, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the World Federation of Trade Unions, 1974; Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the World Federation of Trade Unions, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the World Federation of Trade Unions, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Constitution of the World Federation of Trade Unions, 1990; Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Constitution of the World Federation of Trade Unions, 1990; Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Box: 75, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The World Federation of Trade Unions and Indochina, 1975; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
    Notes: Oct.
  - Item 2: The WFTU and the struggle of the Arab workers and peoples half-yearly bulletin of the WFTU, 1975; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The WFTU and the struggle of the Arab workers and peoples half-yearly bulletin of the WFTU, 1976; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: The WFTU and the struggle of the Arab workers and peoples half-yearly bulletin of the WFTU, 1976; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Earth must not become a desert, 1975; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Human progress depends on peace, 1975; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: The trade unions and the United Nations, 1973; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: The rights of salaried inventor, 1975; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Box: 75, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: 9th World Trade Union Congress, Prague, Czechoslovakia, April 16-23, 1978: [universal declaration of trade union rights]: draft document, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    Author: World Trade Union Congress
  - Item 2: 9th World Trade Union Congress, Prague, Czechoslovakia, April 16-23, 1978: [universal declaration of trade union rights]: draft document, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Document on policy and action: draft, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Document on policy and action: draft, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Mutual recognition of diplomas and degrees, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Trade unions strategies for the 1990s: democratic alternative in the interests of workers and humankind through trade union dialogue and action, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: 2nd International Trade Union Conference for Action against Apartheid: Resolution, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: 12th World Trade Union Congress: Appeal resolutions messages: list of participants, 1990; Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Box: 75, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Flashes from the trade unions, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: For radical changes: World Federation of Trade Unions, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Bulletin of the International Trade Union Committee of Solidarity with the Workers and People of Chile, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: International Trade Union Committee of Solidarity with Workers and People of Chile
  - Item 6: World trade union movement, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: World trade union movement, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Trade unions and the Lome Convention, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Trade unions and the Lome Convention, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.2, Special Issue
  - Item 11: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.3, Special Issue
  - Item 15: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.4, Special Issue
  - Item 17: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: Towards the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.6, Special Issue
  - Item 19: Appeal of the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: Appeal of the 9th World Trade Union Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 21: International economic relations and technology, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 22: International economic relations and technology, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 23: Iran in struggle, 1978; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Box: 75, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Solidarity with Korea, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Trade Unions - Women // Women-Trade Unions, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Trade Union Conference of Latin American and Caribbean Countries on the Problems of Working Women: Panama City, March 8-10, 1979, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Trade Union Conference of Latin American and Caribbean Countries on the Problems of Working Women
  - Item 4: Union strategy against unemployment: 21st session of WFTU Bureau Berlin, 20-22 November, 1979, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: WFTU Bureau
  - Item 5: Vietnam: El derecho esta al lado del Vietnam, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Federation syndicale mondiale
    Notes: Cover only in English, Spanish, French, and Russian
  - Item 6: Vietnam: El derecho esta al lado del Vietnam, 1979; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Notes: Cover only in English, Spanish, French, and Russian. Copy 2.
- Box: 75, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Declaration: 31st Session of the General Council of the WFTU, 1980; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Notes: Moscow, October 1-5, 1980
  - Item 2: Declaration: 31st Session of the General Council of the WFTU, 1980; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Notes: Moscow, October 1-5, 1980. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: 1980-Year of Intensified Action for Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Detente, conversion, disarmament: International Trade Union Round Table: Sofia, Bulgaria, 26 September 1980, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: International Trade Union Round Table
- Box: 75, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Act against apartheid and its foreign accomplices, 1982; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Disarmament, the alternative in our epoch for ensuring the economic and social development of the peoples, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Disarmament, the alternative in our epoch for ensuring the economic and social development of the peoples, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: The impact of micro-technology on workers, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: The impact of micro-technology on workers, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: The impact of micro-technology on workers, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: The impact of micro-technology on workers, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Trade unions and the challenges of the 1980s, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: The dialogue on development and the WFTU, 1981; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Box: 75, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: TNCs Bulletin, 1989; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Economic bulletin, 1983; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.2-3
  - Item 3: Economic bulletin, 1983; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Economic bulletin, 1983; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: A framework for international trade union cooperation: main document, 1986; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: A framework for international trade union cooperation: main document, 1986; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: ILO inquiry rules that Berufsverbote in FRG violate workers' rights, 1987; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: 41st Session of the WFTU General Council, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Box: 75, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: WFTU: unity solidarity peace 1945-1985, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Author: Vsevolod Mozhaev
  - Item 2: WFTU: unity solidarity peace 1945-1985, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: WFTU: unity solidarity peace 1945-1985, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Haymarket heritage: on centenary of Chicago events in May 1886, 1986; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Author: Anatoly Repin
  - Item 5: Young workers of the world towards the 21st century, 1989; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Box: 76, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Unity and United Action of Trade Unions more vital than ever, 1984; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Open letter to the workers and Trade Unions in the United States of America, 1985; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Open letter to the workers and Trade Unions in the United States of America, 1985; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Jobs - not war, 1983; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: paper poster
  - Item 5: Declaration of the World Trade Union Conference on Social and Economic Aspects of Disarmament, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: W.F.T.U.-Arab workers: bulletin of solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1
  - Item 7: W.F.T.U.-Arab workers: bulletin of solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: W.F.T.U.-Arab workers: bulletin of solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: W.F.T.U.-Arab workers: bulletin of solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: W.F.T.U.-Arab workers: bulletin of solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: W.F.T.U.-Arab workers: bulletin of solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Save world peace, 1985; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Save world peace, 1985; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Box: 76, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade unions and the challenges of the 1980s, 1981; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Trade unions and the challenges of the 1980s, 1981; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Appeal and resolutions, 1982; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The WFTU and the Soviet trade unions, 1975; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: P.T. Pimenov
  - Item 5: With our unity and solidarity we shall build a better life for all mankind and meet the challenges of the 1980s!: report, 1981; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Ibrahim Zakaria
  - Item 6: With our unity and solidarity we shall build a better life for all mankind and meet the challenges of the 1980s!: report, 1981; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: With our unity and solidarity we shall build a better life for all mankind and meet the challenges of the 1980s!: report, 1981; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: With our unity and solidarity we shall build a better life for all mankind and meet the challenges of the 1980s: co-report on Latin America and the Caribbean, 1982; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Roberto Veiga
  - Item 9: With our unity and solidarity we shall build a better life for all mankind and meet the challenges of the 1980s: co-report on Latin America and the Caribbean, 1982; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Development issues and trade unions, 1985; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Development issues and trade unions, 1985; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The Arms race: a criminal waste and betrayal of mankind: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: article/flyer
  - Item 13: For a better life: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: For a better life: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Trade Union action for development: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Trade Unions of the Socialist Countries: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Trade Unions of the Socialist Countries: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: United for the defence and respect of human and unions rights: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Advance of united action and trade union unity: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Advance of united action and trade union unity: Towards the 10th World Trade Union Congress, Havana, 10-15 February 1982, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Box: 76, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Statutes of the World Confederation of Labour: Declaration of Principals, Statutes, Internal Regulations, 1986; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Author: World Confederation of Labour